Guide to Major Figures in American Music
Major Figures in American Music
- Stevens, Halsey
  - Stevens, Halsey, undated; OHV 45 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 119 mins
- Still, William Grant
  - Still, William Grant, 1972 November 22; OHV 32 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 141 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Liz Gant
- Stinson, Bill
  - Stinson, Bill, 1977 October 12; OHV 227 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 267 mins; Transcript Page Count: 103 pages
    Newport Beach, CA
  - Stinson, Bill, 1977 October 13; OHV 227 c-e
- Stock, David
  - Stock, David, 1983 September 23; OHV 146 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 219 mins; Transcript Page Count: 105 pages
- Stokes, Eric
  - Stokes, Eric, 1982 December 31; OHV 104 a-d; Transcript Page Count: 65 pages
- Stokowski, Leopold
  - Stokowski, Leopold, 1971 November 22; OHV 16 b; Approximate Running Time: 23 mins
  - Stokowski, Leopold, 1972 February 18; OHV 16 a; Approximate Running Time: 58 mins; Transcript Page Count: 29 pages
- Stoloff, Morris
  - Stoloff, Morris, 1978 March 17; OHV 229 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 65 mins; Transcript Page Count: 29 pages
- Strang, Gerald
  - Strang, Gerald, 1975 March 1; OHV 33 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 112 mins; Transcript Page Count: 57 pages
- Strange, Allen
  - Strange, Allen, 1983 May 15; OHV 124 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 173 mins; Transcript Page Count: 86 pages
- Stravinsky, Igor
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1949 October 19; OHV 345 a; Approximate Running Time: 9 mins
- Strunk, Oliver
  - Strunk, Oliver, 1973 August 8; OHV 25 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 96 mins; Transcript Page Count: 36 pages
    Grotta Ferrata, Italy
- Stucky, Steven
  - Stucky, Steven, 2006 November 16; OHV 341 a; Approximate Running Time: 60 mins
  - Stucky, Steven, 2013 January 11; OHV 341 b-h; Approximate Running Time: 169 mins
- Subotnick, Morton
  - Subotnick, Morton, circa 1967; OHV 111 l-n; Transcript Page Count: 39 pages
  - Subotnick, Morton, 1983 March 21; OHV 111 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 82 mins; Transcript Page Count: 43 pages
  - Subotnick, Morton, 1983 March 29; OHV 111 c; Approximate Running Time: 69 mins
  - Subotnick, Morton, 1983 March 29; OHV v111 R1
  - Subotnick, Morton, 1984 February 29; OHV 111 d; Approximate Running Time: 48 mins; Transcript Page Count: 14 pages
  - Subotnick, Morton, 1992 July 27; OHV 111 e-f; Approximate Running Time: 70 mins
  - Subotnick, Morton, 1998 July 11; OHV 111 g-k; Approximate Running Time: 182 mins; Transcript Page Count: 72 pages
  - Subotnick, Morton, 2016 March 16; OHV 111 o-q; Approximate Running Time: 165 mins
    Cortland, NY
  - Subotnick, Morton, 2018 January 15; OHV 111 r-w; Approximate Running Time: 204 mins
- Suderberg, Robert
  - Suderburg, Robert, 1986 February 4; OHV 559 a
    Suderburg, Robert (1936-01-28-2013-04-22)
- Sudler, Louis
  - Sudler, Louis, 1978 April 30; OHV 62 g-j; Transcript Page Count: 180 pages
  - Sudler, Louis, 1978 February 4; OHV 62 a-c
  - Sudler, Louis, 1978 February 5; OHV 62 d-f
- Sullivan, Maxine
  - Sullivan, Maxine, 1972 October 24; OHV 36 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 129 mins
    Patricia Singleton
- Sur, Donald
  - Sur, Donald, 1986 October 2; OHV 178 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 277 mins; Transcript Page Count: 101 pages
  - Sur, Donald, 1986 October 3; OHV 178 e-j
- Suttor, Matthew
  - Suttor, Matthew, 2011 January 20; OHV 405 a; Approximate Running Time: 69 mins
- Swallow, Steve
  - Swallow, Steve, 2012 July 15; OHV 428 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 129 mins; Transcript Page Count: 43 pages
  - Swallow, Steve, 2012 August 2; OHV 428 d-i; Approximate Running Time: 118 mins; Transcript Page Count: 41 pages
- Swift, Kay
  - Swift, Kay, 1975 May 1; OHV 35 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 105 mins; Transcript Page Count: 52 pages
- Sydeman, William
  - Sydeman, William, circa 1967; OHV 374 a
- Talma, Louise
  - Talma, Louise, circa 1967; OHV 264 b; Transcript Page Count: 4 pages
  - Talma, Louise, 1986 March 23; OHV 264 a; Approximate Running Time: 32 mins
- Tate, Jerod Impichcha̲achaaha̕
  - Tate, Jerod Impichcha̲achaaha̕, 2021 February 17; OHV 545 a; Cobb, Michael (Musician); 1 Computer File; 1.29 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 120 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Oklahoma City, OK and interviewer in Brooklyn, NY.
    Tate, Jerod Impichcha̲achaaha̕, 1968-
- Taylor, Billy
  - Taylor, Billy, 1981 February 6; OHV 76 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 85 mins; Transcript Page Count: 39 pages
  - Taylor, Billy, 1983 April 1; OHV 76 c-d; Approximate Running Time: 89 mins
  - Taylor, Billy, 1983 April 1; OHV v76 R1-2
- Teitelbaum, Richard
  - Teitelbaum, Richard, 2002 August 27; OHV 323 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 208 mins; Transcript Page Count: 100 pages
- Temianka, Henry
  - Temianka, Henry, 1978 April 3–1982 March 30; 1982 March 30; OHV 259 a-c; Transcript Page Count: 21 pages
    Stockholm, Sweden Los Angeles, CA
    Carl Friedner
- Tenney, James
  - Tenney, James, 1988 June 10 1988 June 12; OHV 196 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 173 mins; Transcript Page Count: 71 pages
    Toronto, Ontario, Canada
    Gayle Young
  - Tenney, James, 1996 May 20; OHV 196 e-g; Approximate Running Time: 112 mins; Transcript Page Count: 39 pages
  - Tenney, James, undated; OHV 359 o-p; Approximate Running Time: 91 mins
- Tenzer, Michael
  - Tenzer, Michael, 1993 April 20; OHV 204 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 78 mins; Transcript Page Count: 33 pages
    Mitchell Dyck
  - Tenzer, Michael, 1993 December 9; OHV 204 c-d; Approximate Running Time: 59 mins; Transcript Page Count: 31 pages
    Martin Bresnick
- Testa, Carl
  - Testa, Carl, 2010 November 8; OHV 402 a; Approximate Running Time: 73 mins
    Wesleyan Comp. Seminar
- Theodorakis, Mikis
  - Theodorakis, Mikis, 1978 May 21; OHV 313 a; Approximate Running Time: 21 mins
- Theofanidis, Christopher
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 1997 May 27; OHV 249 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 158 mins; Transcript Page Count: 76 pages
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2008 January 24; OHV 249 e; Approximate Running Time: 38 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2009 November 12; OHV 249 f; Approximate Running Time: 45 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2010 October 7; OHV 249 g; Approximate Running Time: 40 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2011 October 6; OHV 249 h
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2013 April 4; OHV 249 i; Approximate Running Time: 4 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2014 February 28; OHV 249 j-l; Approximate Running Time: 75 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2014 October 30; OHV 249 m-o
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2017 March 8; OHV v249 p; Approximate Running Time: 82 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2017 April 6; OHV 249 q
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2017 November 9; OHV 249 r; Approximate Running Time: 46 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2018 October 11; OHV 249 s; Approximate Running Time: 49 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2019 October 3; OHV 249 t; Approximate Running Time: 52 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2020 September 24; OHV 249 u-v; Theofanidis, Christopher, 1967-; 2 Computer Files; 116 megabytes; Approximate running time: 38 mins
    .mov and .mp4 files
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2021 November 18; OHV 249 w; 1 Computer File; 60 megabytes; Approximate running time: 60 mins
    Theofanidis, Christopher, 1967-
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2022 February 10; OHV 249 x; 1 Computer File; 441 megabytes; Approximate running time: 44 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2023 January 26; OHV 249 y; 1 Computer File; 285 megabytes; Approximate running time: 29 mins
  - Theofanidis, Christopher, 2024 January 25; OHV 249 z; 1 Computer File; 339 megabytes; Approximate running time: 34 mins
- Thomas, Augusta Read
  - Thomas, Augusta Read, 2003 September 24; OHV 334 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 117 mins; Transcript Page Count: 65 pages
    Becket, Mass
    Jenny Raymond
  - Thomas, Augusta Read, 2004 November 4; OHV 334 d-g; Approximate Running Time: 126 mins
- Thomas, Michael Tilson
  - Thomas, Michael Tilson, 1986 October 7; OHV 379 a; Approximate Running Time: 66 mins
  - Thomas, Michael Tilson, 1994 March 28; OHV 379 b; Approximate Running Time: 30 mins
- Thome, Joel
  - Thome, Joel, 2012 July 17; OHV 427 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 83 mins
- Thompson, Randall
  - Thompson, Randall, 1973 October 18; OHV 59 a; Transcript Page Count: 12 pages
    Jean Bonin
- Thomson, Virgil
  - Thomson, Virgil, circa 1967; OHV 29 ww
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1976 October 18; OHV 29 j; Kretschmer, Joan Thomson; Approximate Running Time: 32 mins; Transcript Page Count: 15 pages
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1977 September 28; OHV 29 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 206 mins; Transcript Page Count: 70 pages
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1978 January 10; OHV 29 e-g
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1978 June 6; OHV v29 R1
    Esther Harriott
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1978 June 23; OHV v29a R1-6
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1978 June 23; OHV 29 k-l; Approximate Running Time: 57 mins
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1979 June 6; OHV 29 o; Approximate Running Time: 60 mins; Transcript Page Count: 23 pages
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 January 15; OHV 29 q-r
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 January 22; OHV 29 s-t
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 January 29; OHV 29 u-x
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 February 12; OHV 29 y-aa
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 February 19; OHV 29 bb-ee
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 February 26; OHV 29 ff-hh
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 March 25; OHV 29 ii-ll
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 April 8; OHV 29 mm-oo
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 April 15; OHV 29 pp-qq
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 April 22; OHV 29 rr-tt
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1980 September 26; OHV 29 m; Transcript Page Count: 10 pages
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1983 July 7; OHV 29 h; Approximate Running Time: 30 mins; Transcript Page Count: 9 pages
    Eric Martin
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1986 December 6; OHV 29 p
    Baltimore, MD
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1987; OHV 29 n; Transcript Page Count: 11 pages
    David Dubal, Jake Holmes (announcer)
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1987 January 1; OHV 29 uu; Approximate Running Time: 34 mins
  - Thomson, Virgil, 2016 November 24; OHV 29 vv; Approximate Running Time: 22 mins
- Thorne, Francis
  - Thorne, Francis, 1987 April 28; OHV 192 a-g; Approximate Running Time: 194 mins; Transcript Page Count: 80 pages
- Threadgill, Henry
  - Threadgill, Henry, 2016 January 22; OHV 487 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 162 mins
- Torke, Michael
  - Torke, Michael, 1986 November 13; OHV 188 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 57 mins; Transcript Page Count: 21 pages
  - Torke, Michael, 1987 June 8; OHV 188 c; Approximate Running Time: 29 mins
    David Garland
  - Torke, Michael, 1991; OHV 188 e; Approximate Running Time: 16 mins
    Unknown Interviewer on Side e?David Zinman, conductor, included on Side f
  - Torke, Michael, 1991 January 24; OHV 188 g; Approximate Running Time: 18 mins
    Side g - David Sterns - commentary?Side h - John Harle, saxophonist and unidentified Interviewer
  - Torke, Michael, 1992; OHV 188 f
  - Torke, Michael, 1992 February 3; OHV 188 d; Approximate Running Time: 8 mins
    London, England
  - Torke, Michael, 1995 September 10; OHV 188 h
  - Torke, Michael, 1999 July 27; OHV 188 j-n; Approximate Running Time: 206 mins; Transcript Page Count: 81 pages
  - Torke, Michael, 2018 October 4; OHV 188 o; Approximate Running Time: 48 mins
  - Torke, Michael, undated; OHV 188 i; Approximate Running Time: 32 mins
- Tower, Joan
  - Tower, Joan, 1976 January 9; OHV 55 a-b; Harmeyer, Frances; Approximate Running Time: 56 mins; Transcript Page Count: 19 pages
    Tower, Joan, 1938-
  - Tower, Joan, 1983 July 28; OHV 55 c-d; Fournier, Janice E.; Approximate Running Time: 60 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
  - Tower, Joan, 1993 July 30; OHV 55 e-f; Niemeyer, Julie Ann; Approximate Running Time: 52 mins; Transcript Page Count: 20 pages
  - Tower, Joan, 1998 July 4; OHV 55 g-h; Raymond, Jenny; Approximate Running Time: 98 mins; Transcript Page Count: 38 pages
  - Tower, Joan, 2017 July 30; OHV 55 i; Approximate Running Time: 78 mins
- Trueman, Dan
  - Trueman, Dan, 2018 February 1; OHV 506 a
- Tudor, David
  - Tudor, David, 1986 April 7; OHV 241 s-t; Approximate Running Time: 83 mins
  - Tudor, David, 1992 August 3; OHV 241 m-q; Approximate Running Time: 184 mins; Transcript Page Count: 40 pages
    Stony Point, NY
    John Holzaepfel
  - Tudor, David, 1995 July 12; OHV 241 r; Approximate Running Time: 39 mins; Transcript Page Count: 11 pages
    Jack Vees and unidentified
  - Tudor, David, 1995 July 19; OHV 241 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 278 mins
  - Tudor, David, 1995 August 6; OHV 241 e-f
  - Tudor, David, 1995 September 18; OHV 241 g-h
  - Tudor, David, 1995 October 11; OHV 241 i-j; Approximate Running Time: 94 mins
    Jack Vees and Christian Wolff
  - Tudor, David, 1995 December 6; OHV 241 k-l; Approximate Running Time: 79 mins
    Jack Vees and Pauline Oliveros
  - Tudor, David / Cage, John, undated; OHV v41b R1-2
- Ueno, Ken
  - Ueno, Ken, 2013 January 24; OHV 437 a; Approximate Running Time: 64 mins
- Ung, Chinary
  - Ung, Chinary, 2013 March 17; OHV 456 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 122 mins
- Ussachevsky, Vladimir
  - Ussachevsky, Vladimir, circa 1967; OHV 201 x-y; Transcript Page Count: 7 pages
  - Ussachevsky, Vladimir, 1977 February 17; OHV 201 a-g; Kretschmer, Joan Thomson; Approximate Running Time: 424 mins; Transcript Page Count: 204 pages
  - Ussachevsky, Vladimir, 1977 April 14 1977 April 28; OHV 201 h-l; Kretschmer, Joan Thomson
  - Ussachevsky, Vladimir, 1978 April 18; OHV 201 m-w; Kretschmer, Joan Thomson; Approximate Running Time: 406 mins; Transcript Page Count: 205-?455 pages
  - Ussachevsky, Vladimir, with Robert Moog, Tom Rhea, and Konstantin Simonovitch, 1979 February 1; OHV 201 x; Kretschmer, Joan Thomson; 1 Audiocassette (Box 39002038321791, Item barcode 39002038326295, Box 39002038321932, Item barcode 39002038326303)
    Panel on electronic music held at Hofstra Universith in Hempstead, NY
    Ussachevsky, Vladimir, 1911-1990; Moog, Bob (Robert) (1934-05-23-2005-08-21); Rhea, Tom; Simonovic, Konstantin (1923-)
- Van de Vate, Nancy
  - Van de Vate, Nancy, 1988 January 8; OHV 199 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 183 mins
  - Van de Vate, Nancy, 1988 April 15; OHV 199 d-h
- Varese, Edgard
  - Varese, Edgard, 1959 September 1; OHV 134 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 35 mins; Transcript Page Count: 16 pages
  - Varese, Edgard, 1965 May 4; OHV 134 c; Approximate Running Time: 95 mins; Transcript Page Count: 21 pages
    Chou Wen-chung, L. Altman, with Louise Varese
  - Varese, Edgard, 1965 May 18; OHV 134 d; Approximate Running Time: 129 mins; Transcript Page Count: 22 pages
  - Varese, Edgard, 1965 May 29; OHV 134 h-i; Approximate Running Time: 89 mins; Transcript Page Count: 45 pages
    Chou Wen-chung, L. Altman with Lousie Varese
  - Varese, Edgard, 1965 June 12; OHV 134 l-o; Approximate Running Time: 79 mins
    Chou Wen Chung
  - Varese, Edgard, 1965 June 22; OHV 134 e; Approximate Running Time: 50 mins; Transcript Page Count: 14 pages
  - Varese, Edgard, 1965 November 14; OHV 134 j-k; Approximate Running Time: 93 mins
    Chou Wen-chung, L. Altman with Louise Varese
  - Varese, Edgard, 1965 November 21; OHV 134 f-g; Approximate Running Time: 125 mins; Transcript Page Count: 34 pages
- Vees, Jack
  - Vees, Jack, 1993 December 16; OHV 236 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 56 mins; Transcript Page Count: 27 pages
  - Vees, Jack, 1998 August 27; OHV 236 c-d; Approximate Running Time: 275 mins; Transcript Page Count: 119 pages
  - Vees, Jack, 1998 September 1; OHV 236 e-i
  - Vees, Jack, 2007 October 4; OHV 236 j; Approximate Running Time: 40 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2009 November 19; OHV 236 k; Approximate Running Time: 36 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2010 November 4; OHV 236 l; Approximate Running Time: 103 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2011 December 1; OHV 236 m; Approximate Running Time: 16 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2013 April 11; OHV 236 n-o; Approximate Running Time: 101 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2013 October 17; OHV 236 p; Approximate Running Time: 35 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2014 February 19; OHV v236 q
  - Vees, Jack, 2014 February 19; OHV 236 q; Approximate Running Time: 57 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2015 April 16; OHV 236 r-v; Approximate Running Time: 21 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2015 October 8; OHV 236 w; Approximate Running Time: 6 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2017 February 2; OHV 236 y; Approximate Running Time: 72 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2016 February 18; OHV 236 x; Approximate Running Time: 28 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2018 April 12; OHV 236 z; Approximate Running Time: 43 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2019 April 4; OHV 236 aa; Approximate running time: 25 mins
    Vees, Jack (1955-)
  - Vees, Jack, 2019 December 5; OHV 236 bb; Approximate running time: 64 mins
    Interview Location:
    Year erroneously stated as 2020 in audio ID. Recording is interrupted at approximately 20 seconds, due to a power cut.
  - Vees, Jack, 2021 March 25; OHV 236 cc; 1 Computer File; 432 megabytes; Approximate running time: 26 mins
  - Vees, Jack, 2022 April 21; OHV 236 dd-ee; 2 Computer Files; 664 megabytes; Approximate running time: 25 mins
    .wav and .aiff files
    Track OHV 236 ee is a recording of music by Mel Powell, which is discussed in the seminar.
  - Vees, Jack, 2023 April 20; OHV 236 ff; 1 Computer File; 583 megabytes; Approximate running time: 58 mins
    Composition seminar presented by Jack Vees at the Yale School of Music in New Haven, CT
- Vercoe, Elizabeth
  - Vercoe, Elizabeth, 1985 March 4; OHV 167 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 58 mins; Transcript Page Count: 29 pages
    Concord, MA
- Vercoe, Barry
  - Vercoe, Barry, 1978 March 31; OHV 208 a-e; Kretschmer, Joan Thomson; Approximate Running Time: 167 mins
    MIT, Cambridge, MA
- Verdery, Benjamin
  - Verdery, Benjamin, 2010 November 18; OHV v403 a
  - Verdery, Benjamin, 2020 September 7; OHV 403 b-i; Van Cleve, Libby; 8 Computer Files; 4.01 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 270 mins
    Verdery, Benjamin
  - Verdery, Benjamin, 2020 September 15; OHV 403 j-n; Van Cleve, Libby; 5 Computer Files; 3.95 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 268 mins
  - Verdery, Benjamin, 2020 September 16; OHV 403 o-p; Van Cleve, Libby; 3 Computer Files; 1.22 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 83 mins
- Vierk, Lois V
  - Vierk, Lois V, 2004 February 25; OHV 337 a-e; Transcript Page Count: 105 pages
    West, N.Y., N.J.
- Wadley, Jay
  - Wadley, Jay, 2022 April 7; OHV 562 a; 1 Computer File; 730 megabytes; Approximate running time: 72 mins
    Wadley, Jay
- Wagner, Melinda
  - Wagner, Melinda, 2018 July 24; OHV 517 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 105 mins
    Ridgewood, NJ
- Ward, Robert
  - Ward, Robert, 1985 June 20; OHV 358 a; Approximate Running Time: 63 mins
    Chicago, IL (1985) and Evanston, IL(2000)
  - Ward, Robert, 2000 February 25; OHV 358 b; Approximate Running Time: 53 mins; Transcript Page Count: 9 pages
    Evanston, IL
- Warfield, William
  - Warfield, William, 2001 April 27; OHV MC 113
    NEC, Boston, MA
    M. Pfeiffenberger
- Warren, Richard
  - Warren, Richard, 2007 January 12; OHV MCD18
- Washburn, Abigail
  - Washburn, Abigail, 2024 March 1; OHV 592 a; Vees, Jack (1955-); 1 Computer File; 2.08 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 141 mins
    Washburn, Abigail
  - Washburn, Abigail, 2024 March 2; OHV 592 b; Vees, Jack (1955-); 1 Computer File; 982 megabytes; Approximate running time: 65 mins
- Wein, George
  - Wein, George, 1983 March 1; OHV 112 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 70 mins; Transcript Page Count: 34 pages
    Easton, CT
    Harriett Milnes
- Weisgall, Hugo
  - Weisgall, Hugo, 1981 December 19; OHV 92 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 233 mins; Transcript Page Count: 105 pages
    Great Neck, NY
  - Weisgall, Hugo, 1982 January 5; OHV 92 c-f
- Wernick, Richard
  - Wernick, Richard, 1983 October 11; OHV 149 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 192 mins; Transcript Page Count: 90 pages
- Wheeler, Scott
  - Wheeler, Scott, undated; OHV 89 b-d; Wheeler, Scott, 1952-
  - Wheeler, Scott, 1992 July 31; OHV 89 a; Approximate Running Time: 46 mins; Transcript Page Count: 19 pages
- White, Lenny
  - White, Lenny, 2022 August 16; OHV 566 a-f; Bendian, Gregg; 6 Computer Files; 6.2 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 191 mins
    Fair Lawn, NJ
    White, Lenny (1949-12-19-)
  - White, Lenny, 2022 August 17; OHV 566 g-i; Bendian, Gregg; 3 Computer Files; 4.2 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 69 mins
    Teaneck, NJ
- Williams, Amy
  - Williams, Amy, 2016 March 2; OHV 498 a; Approximate Running Time: 83 mins
- Williams, Jan
  - Williams, Jan, 2022 May 9; OHV 563 a; Perry, Jeffrey; 2 Computer Files; 1.06 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 107 mins
    Interview conducted over videochat with interviewee in Buffalo, NY.
  - Williams, Jan, 2022 May 16; OHV 563 b; Perry, Jeffrey; 1 Computer File; 830 megabytes; Approximate running time: 118 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Buffalo, NY.
- Williams, John
  - Williams, John, 1985 August 28; OHV 354 a; Approximate Running Time: 58 mins
- Williams, Mary Lou
  - Williams, Mary Lou, 1981 March 16; OHV 77 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 184 mins; Transcript Page Count: 78 pages
- Wilson, Gerald
  - Wilson, Gerald, 2014 January 7; OHV 463 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 108 mins
- Wilson, Keith
  - Wilson, Keith, 2007 October 5; OHV 383 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 121 mins; Transcript Page Count: 59 pages
- Wilson, Olly
  - Wilson, Olly, 1983 September 21; OHV 144 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 169 mins; Transcript Page Count: 78 pages
  - Wilson, Olly, 1997 June 19; OHV 144 e-g; Approximate Running Time: 126 mins; Transcript Page Count: 50 pages
- Wilson, Richard
  - Wilson, Richard, 1993 December 1; OHV 293 a; Approximate Running Time: 32 mins; Transcript Page Count: 13 pages
    Steve Sullivan
  - Wilson, Richard, 2004 November 17; OHV 293 b-d; Approximate Running Time: 144 mins; Transcript Page Count: 58 pages
    Ed Harsh
- Winans, BeBe
  - Winans, BeBe, 2024 April 18; OHV 595 a; Dromgoole, Ambre; 1 Computer File; 8.61 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 60 mins
    Winans, BeBe
- Winsor, Phil
  - Winsor, Phil, 1983 September 29; OHV 151 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 200 mins; Transcript Page Count: 119 pages
- Wolfe, Julia
  - Wolfe, Julia, 1997 August 14; OHV 255 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 209 mins; Transcript Page Count: 101 pages
  - Wolfe, Julia, 2011 June 14; OHV 255 f; Approximate Running Time: 25 mins
    Mary Lou Aleskie
  - Wolfe, Julia, 2013 January 17; OHV 255 g; Approximate Running Time: 59 mins
  - Wolfe, Julia, 2014 July 27; OHV 255 h-m; Approximate Running Time: 174 mins
- Wolff, Christian
  - Wolff, Christian, 1984 September 21; OHV 174 m; Approximate Running Time: 35 mins; Transcript Page Count: 9 pages
    Hanover, NH
  - Wolff, Christian, 1985 December 30; OHV 174 a-g; Approximate Running Time: 132 mins; Transcript Page Count: 76 pages
  - Wolff, Christian, 1985 December 31; OHV 174 h-j; Approximate Running Time: 86 mins; Transcript Page Count: 33 pages
  - Wolff, Christian, 1986 April 26; OHV 174 k-l; Approximate Running Time: 40 mins; Transcript Page Count: 16 pages
  - Wolff, Christian, 1997 July; OHV 174 p-q; Approximate Running Time: 83 mins; Transcript Page Count: 33 pages
    Royalton, VT
  - Wolff, Christian, 1997 July 26; OHV 174 n-o; Approximate Running Time: 75 mins; Transcript Page Count: 31 pages
  - Wolff, Christian, 2002 December 13; OHV 174 r-s
    This material is restricted. Access may be granted to a patron who has obtained direct permission from the interviewer for this interview, Rebecca Kim.
  - Wolff, Jonathan, 2017 January 26; OHV 496 a; Approximate Running Time: 75 mins
    Yale Undergraduate Composition Class
- Wolpe, Stefan
  - Wolpe, Stefan, 1971 October 17; OHV 5 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 201 mins; Transcript Page Count: 25 pages
    Westbeth, NY
  - Wople, Stefan, 1971 December 16; OHV 5 d-f
- Woods, Phil
  - Woods, Phil, 2013 June 12; OHV 452 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 130 mins; Transcript Page Count: 81 pages
    Delaware Water Gap, PA
- Woolf, Randall